Guide to the Edward J. McCluskey Papers SC1112
Department of Special Collections and University Archives
- Administrative files
  - RATs, 2000 Winter (Box 30, Folder 24)
  - RATs, 1999 Fall (Box 30, Folder 25)
  - RATs, 1999 June (Box 30, Folder 26)
  - RATs, 1999 Spring (Box 30, Folder 27)
  - RATs, 1998-1999 (Box 30, Folder 28)
  - IDDQ Program, 1998 (Box 30, Folder 29)
  - RATs 385, 1998 Spring (Box 30, Folder 30)
  - RATs, 1997 Fall (Box 30, Folder 31)
  - EE 489 Reduced Lecture Notes, 1998 Feb. (Box 30, Folder 32)
  - Research - Space Allocation + Academic, 1998 Jan. 20 (Box 30, Folder 33)
  - Mike Kondrat - Visit to Stanford, 1998 Jan. 21 (Box 30, Folder 34)
  - Conferences, 1997 (Box 30, Folder 35)
  - Rats - old, 1997 Sept.-Oct. (Box 30, Folder 36)
  - EE 275 = Module 2, 1996-1998 (Box 30, Folder 37)
  - Visiting Committee Report, 1997 Dec. 16 (Box 30, Folder 38)
  - CSL Info., 1997-1998 (Box 30, Folder 39)
  - AD Com, 1969 (Box 30, Folder 40)
  - SRI, 1967 (Box 30, Folder 41)
  - NSF External Proposals, 1969-1974 (Box 30, Folder 42)
  - CS Comprehensive Exam Questions, 1967-1977 (Box 30, Folder 43)
  - NASA Symposium, Talks, 1974-1976 (Box 30, Folder 44)
  - NASA Correspondence, 1974-1976 (Box 30, Folder 45)
  - NASA Research Info, 1972-1976 (Box 30, Folder 46)
  - HRUBY Rept. (NASA), 1976 (Box 30, Folder 47)
  - Recovery Papers (Box 31, Folder 1)
  - SIRU (Miscl) (Box 31, Folder 2)
  - SIRU/NASA Reports (Box 31, Folder 3)
  - Spartan Book - Transients - Paper Original (Box 31, Folder 4)
  - Riordan (Box 31, Folder 5)
  - John Riordan (Box 31, Folder 6)
  - Whirlwind Computers (Box 31, Folder 7)
  - Computer Courses at Stanford - Correspondences & Manuals, 1963-1967 (Box 31, Folder 8)
  - Binder - RATS (Box 31, Folder 9)
  - MSI (Box 31, Folder 11)
  - An Analysis of the 7474 (Box 31, Folder 12)
  - IBM Europe Institute - Part 1, 1985 Jun (Box 31, Folder 14)
  - IBM Europe Institute - Part 2, 1985 Jun (Box 31, Folder 15)
  - IBM Europe Institute - Part 3, 1985 Jun (Box 31, Folder 16)
  - NASA (Box 31, Folder 17)
  - Trip to Draper Labs - MIT, 1973 Nov 12-13 (Box 31, Folder 18)
  - NASA Budget - Clock Memo (Box 31, Folder 19)
  - MIT - Design of a Duel Computer Configuration for Redundant Computation - Bruce Ressler, 1973 Jun (Box 31, Folder 20)
  - NASA (Box 31, Folder 21)
  - SF NASA (Box 31, Folder 22)
  - NASA - OLLS (Box 31, Folder 23)
  - ARPA - Release of SOW (Box 31, Folder 24)
  - Winfred Schneeweis - RE: Visit/Talk @ CRC (Box 31, Folder 25)
  - Winfred Schneeweiss (Box 31, Folder 26)
  - Jim Alexiou - Meeting Summary (Box 31, Folder 27)
  - ONR Final Report (Box 33, Folder 1)
  - ONR Report, 1992 Jul (Box 33, Folder 2)
  - ONR Report, 1991 (Box 33, Folder 3)
  - ONR Report, 1989 Nov 28 (Box 33, Folder 4)
  - ONR Report, 1989 Jul (Box 33, Folder 5)
  - ONR Report, 1989 Feb 14 (Box 33, Folder 6)
  - ONR Proposal to ID - New Version, 1988 Feb 19 (Box 33, Folder 7)
  - ONR - Budget Proposal (Box 33, Folder 8)
  - ONR Receipt of Proposal (Box 33, Folder 9)
  - Logic Design Principals - Part 1 (Pages 1-375), 1999 (Box 33, Folder 10)
  - Logic Design Principals - Part 2 (Pages 376-547), 1999 (Box 33, Folder 11)
  - Digital Test Principles (Box 33, Folder 12)
  - Stanford Electronics Laboratory, 1973-1974 (Box 34, Folder 7)
  - RATs Handouts, 1971 (Box 34, Folder 8)
  - RATs Bibliography, 1981 Jan. (Box 34, Folder 9)
  - Reading List for an Introduction to the Field of Reliability and Testing, 1972 Aug. 22 (Box 34, Folder 10)
- Subject files
  - Edward J. McClusky Tribute, 2004 Oct 10 (Box 6, Folder 1)
  - Van de Goor, A. J. Dr. (Box 6, Folder 2)
  - Van Voorhis, Dave (Box 6, Folder 3)
  - Van Nostrand Reinhold Company (Box 6, Folder 4)
  - Vantage (Box 6, Folder 5)
  - Velardi, Paola (Box 6, Folder 6)
  - Verdillon, Andre (Box 6, Folder 7)
  - VHDL (Box 6, Folder 8)
  - Viewlogic (Box 6, Folder 9)
  - Vinsani, Mario (Box 6, Folder 10)
  - Visiting Scholar (Box 6, Folder 11)
  - Wakerly, John F. (Box 6, Folder 12)
  - Wang, Jufang (Box 6, Folder 13)
  - Wang, Laung-Terng (Box 6, Folder 14)
  - Wattal, Sanjay (Box 6, Folder 15)
  - Wiley, John & Sons, Inc. Publishers (Box 6, Folder 16)
  - Wilken, Kent - Recommend (Box 6, Folder 17)
  - Wakerly, John (Box 6, Folder 18)
  - Wang, Laung-Terng (Box 6, Folder 19)
  - Who's Who (Box 6, Folder 20)
  - Wiederhold, Gio (Box 6, Folder 21)
  - Wunderlich, Hans-Joachim (Box 6, Folder 22)
  - Dong Xiang - Visiting Scholar Applicant (Box 6, Folder 23)
  - Xianglin, Xi (Box 6, Folder 24)
  - Xilinx, Inc. (Box 6, Folder 25)
  - Xilinx-NDA (Box 6, Folder 26)
  - Xu, Xingning (Box 6, Folder 27)
  - Yamada, Teruhiko, 1993 Mar-Sep (Box 6, Folder 28)
  - Yamauchi, Hisashi (Box 6, Folder 29)
  - Yamamura, Hideho (Box 6, Folder 30)
  - Yan, Xu (Box 6, Folder 31)
  - Yarmolik, V. N. (Box 6, Folder 32)
  - Yee, Gin (Box 6, Folder 33)
  - Ying, Zhang (Box 6, Folder 34)
  - Yokoyama, Hiroshi (Box 6, Folder 35)
  - Yoon, Yoonjin (Box 6, Folder 36)
  - Yun, Kenneth (Box 6, Folder 37)
  - Hassan, Syed Zahoor (Box 6, Folder 38)
  - Zasio, John (Box 6, Folder 39)
  - Zukrevskii, Azkadii Prof. (Box 6, Folder 40)
  - Zarrinfar, Farzad (Box 6, Folder 41)
  - Zeng, Chaohuang (Box 6, Folder 42)
  - Zhao, Wei (Box 6, Folder 43)
  - Zhuge, Feng (Box 6, Folder 45)
  - Zorian, Yervant (Box 6, Folder 45)
  - Avra 92-Orthogonal Built-In Self-Test, 1992 Feb 24-28 (Box 6, Folder 46)
- Teaching files
  - EE 275 Review Session RS 2, 1998 Dec. 3; 0 (Box 7)
  - EE 275 Review Session RS 1, 1998 Oct. 26; 0 (Box 7)
  - EE 275 McCluskey #3, 1998 Oct. 1; 1 videotape(s) (vhs) (Box 7)
  - EE 275 McCluskey #2, 1998 Sept. 29; 1 videotape(s) (vhs) (Box 7)
  - EE 275 McCluskey #8, 1998 Oct. 20; 1 videotape(s) (vhs) (Box 7)
  - EE 275 McCluskey #6, 1998 Oct. 13; 1 videotape(s) (vhs) (Box 7)
  - EE 275 McCluskey #5, 1998 Oct. 8; 1 videotape(s) (vhs) (Box 7)
  - EE 275 RS #3, 1998 Dec. 4; 1 videotape(s) (vhs) (Box 7)
  - EE 275 McCluskey #13, 1998 Nov. 10; 1 videotape(s) (vhs) (Box 7)
  - EE 275 McCluskey # 19, 1998 Dec. 3; 1 videotape(s) (vhs) (Box 7)
  - EE 275 McCluskey #18, 1998 Dec. 1; 1 videotape(s) (vhs) (Box 7)
  - EE 275 McCluskey #1, 1998 Sept. 24; 1 videotape(s) (vhs) (Box 7)
  - EE 275 McCluskey #7, 1998 Oct. 15; 1 videotape(s) (vhs) (Box 7)
  - EE 275 McCluskey #9, 1998 Oct. 22; 1 videotape(s) (vhs) (Box 7)
  - EE 275 McCluskey #11, 1998 Nov.3; 1 videotape(s) (vhs) (Box 7)
  - EE 275 McCluskey #14, 1998 Nov. 12; 1 videotape(s) (vhs) (Box 7)
  - EE 275 McCluskey #12, 1998 Nov. 5; 1 videotape(s) (vhs) (Box 7)
  - EE 275 McCluskey #10, 1998 Oct. 29; 1 videotape(s) (vhs) (Box 7)
  - EE 275 McCluskey # 17, 1998 Nov. 24; 1 videotape(s) (vhs) (Box 7)
  - EE 275 McCluskey #16, 1998 Nov. 19; 1 videotape(s) (vhs) (Box 7)
  - EE 275 McCluskey #15, 1998 Nov. 17; 1 videotape(s) (vhs) (Box 7)
  - EE 275 McCluskey #4, 1998 Oct. 6; 1 videotape(s) (vhs) (Box 7)
  - EE 275 Handouts, 2002 Winter (Box 8, Folder 1)
  - EE 275 Handouts, 2001 Autumn (Box 8, Folder 2)
  - EE 275 Handouts, 2002 Autumn (Box 8, Folder 3)
  - EE 275, 2003 Winter (Box 8, Folder 4)
  - EE 275, 2003 Autumn (Box 8, Folder 5)
  - EE 275 Logic Design Principles, 1997 Fall (Box 8, Folder 6)
  - EE 275 Logic Design Principles (Prof. Saxena), 1986 (Box 8, Folder 7)
  - EE 489/ CS 317 Lecture Notes, 1998 Spring (Box 8, Folder 8)
  - EE 488, 1997 Spring (Box 8, Folder 9)
  - EE 488 Handouts, 2002 Spring (Box 8, Folder 10)
  - EE 488 Handouts, 2004 Spring (Box 8, Folder 11)
  - EE275 Original Handouts, 1997-1998 Autumn (Box 9, Folder 1)
  - EE275 Original Handouts, 1997-1998 Winter (Box 9, Folder 2)
  - EE275 Original Handouts, 1998-1998 Autumn (Box 9, Folder 3)
  - EE275 Original Handouts, 1998-1999 Winter (Box 9, Folder 4)
  - EE275 Original Handouts, 1989-1999 Summer (Box 9, Folder 5)
  - EE275 Original Handouts, 1999-2000 Autumn (Box 9, Folder 6)
  - EE275 Original Handouts, 1999-2000 Winter (Box 9, Folder 7)
  - EE275 Original Handouts, 2000-2001 Autumn (Box 9, Folder 8)
  - EE275 Original Handouts, 2000-2001 Winter (Box 10, Folder 1)
  - EE275 Original Copy, 200-2001 Winter (Box 10, Folder 2)
  - EE381 EJM Original Copy, 1992-1993 Autumn (Box 10, Folder 3)
  - EE 381 EJM Original Copy, 1992-1993 Winter (Box 10, Folder 4)
  - EE 381 R. Norwood Orginal's, 1992-1993 Summer (Box 10, Folder 5)
  - EE 381 EJM Original Copy, 1996-1994 Autumn (Box 10, Folder 6)
  - EE 381 EJM Original Copy, 1993-1994 Winter (Box 10, Folder 7)
  - EE 381 EJM Original Handouts, 1994-1995 Autumn (Box 10, Folder 8)
  - EE 381 J. Khakbaz Original Handouts, 1995-1996 Autumn (Box 10, Folder 9)
  - Logic Design Principles EE381-Cs211, 1994-1995 Winter (Box 10, Folder 10)
  - EE 381 Dr. N. Saxena Duplicate Handouts, 1995-1996 Winter (Box 10, Folder 11)
  - EE 381 EJM Orginal Copy, 1994-1995 Winter (Box 10, Folder 12)
  - EE381 - Winter Qtr. - Original Handouts, 1995-1996 (Box 11)
  - EE381 - Winter Qtr. - Duplicate Handouts, 1995-1996 (Box 11)
  - EE381 - Autumn Quarter - Original Handouts, 1996-1997 (Box 11)
  - EE381 - Winter Quarter - Original Handouts, 1996-1997 (Box 11)
  - EE488/ CS381 - Spring Qtr. - Testing Aspects of Computer System, 1984-1985 (Box 11)
  - Chron Files, 1988 (Box 11)
  - Chron Files, 1993-1994 (Box 11)
  - Chron Files, 1989-1990 (Box 11)
  - Chron Files, 1992 (Box 11)
  - Chron Files, 1995 (Box 11)
  - EE 488 Prof. McCluskey Original Handouts, 1988-1989 Spring (Box 13, Folder 1)
  - EE 448 Prof. E. J. McCluskey Lecture Notes Only, 1988-1989 Spring (Box 13, Folder 2)
  - EE Saxena Original handouts, 1990-1991 Spring (Box 13, Folder 3)
  - EE 488 EJM Original Copy, 1992-1993 Spring (Box 13, Folder 4)
  - EE 148 Lecture Notes Only, 1994-1995 Spring (Box 13, Folder 5)
  - EE 148 Lecture Notes Only, 1996-1997 Spring (Box 13, Folder 6)
  - EE 148 EJM Duplicate Copy, 1994-1995 Spring (Box 13, Folder 7)
  - EE488 Original Lecture Notes, 1996-1997 Spring (Box 13, Folder 8)
  - EE488, 1999-2000 Spring (Box 13, Folder 9)
  - EE 488 Handouts, 2001-2002 Spring (Box 13, Folder 10)
  - EE 489, 1984 Spring (Box 14, Folder 1)
  - EE 489, 1984 Spring (Box 14, Folder 2)
  - EE 489 Fault Tolerant Computing Systems, 1984 Spring (Box 14, Folder 3)
  - EE 489 Fault Tolerant Computing Systems, 1998 Spring (Box 14, Folder 4)
  - EE 489 (Box 14, Folder 5)
  - EE 489 Original Copy, 1990 Spring (Box 14, Folder 6)
  - EE 489 Original Handouts, 1992 Spring (Box 14, Folder 7)
  - EE 489, 1994 Spring (Box 14, Folder 8)
  - EE 489, 1994 Spring (Box 14, Folder 9)
  - EE 489/ CS 317 Original Handouts, 1998 Spring (Box 14, Folder 10)
  - EE381, 1996 Oct 8-17; 1 videotape(s) (vhs) (Box 15)
  - EE381, 1996 Oct 10; 1 videotape(s) (vhs) (Box 15)
  - EE518 Files, 1996 May 18 (Box 15)
  - EE381 Files, 1978-1979 (Box 15)
  - EE281 Files, 1979 (Box 15)
  - EE489 - Spring Qtr. Handouts, 1991-1992 (Box 15)
  - EE488 - Spring Quarter Handouts - Duplicates, 1988-1989 (Box 15)
  - EE488 - Spring Quarter Handouts, 1992-1993 (Box 15)
  - EE480 - Spring Quarter Handouts - Duplicate, 1989-1990 (Box 15)
  - CH 7. - SEQ (Box 15)
    - NASA Statees Report (Box 15, Folder 10)
    - ARO (Box 15, Folder 11)
    - ARO (Box 15, Folder 12)
    - ARO (Box 15, Folder 13)
    - ARO Proposal Comments - To B. Dace (Box 15, Folder 14)
    - ARO 8-84 (Box 15, Folder 15)
    - NASA Contract Mod. (Box 15, Folder 16)
    - BMD (Box 15, Folder 17)
    - AROD (Box 15, Folder 18)
    - ARO - Proposal (Box 15, Folder 19)
    - AROD (Box 15, Folder 20)
    - DA 12/83 Rep (Box 15, Folder 21)
  - References - Master List, 1970-1979 (Box 15)
  - PhD's Supervised (Box 15)
  - "RATS" Presentations "385A", 2006 (Box 16, Folder 1)
  - EE 488 Grades, 2004 Spring (Box 16, Folder 2)
  - EE 488 Final Exam and Midterm, 2004 Spring (Box 16, Folder 3)
  - EE 275 Grades- Axess, 2003-2004 Winter (Box 16, Folder 4)
  - EE 275 Final Exam, 2003-2004 Winter (Box 16, Folder 5)
  - EE 275 Midterm, 2003-2004 Winter (Box 16, Folder 6)
  - Grades Axess, 2002-2003 Autumn (Box 16, Folder 7)
  - EE 275 Exam, 2003 December 8 (Box 16, Folder 8)
  - EE 275 Midterm, 2003-2004 Autumn (Box 16, Folder 9)
  - EE 275 Midterm, 2002-2003 Winter (Box 16, Folder 10)
  - EE 275 Midterm, 2002 Fall (Box 16, Folder 11)
  - EE 275 Final Results, 2001-2002 Winter (Box 16, Folder 12)
  - Misc. Grade Rosters, 2001-2002 (Box 16, Folder 13)
  - EE 275, 2001-2002 Fall (Box 16, Folder 14)
  - EE 275, 2000 Autumn (Box 16, Folder 15)
  - EE 275, 2001-2002 Autumn (Box 16, Folder 16)
  - EE 275, 2000 Winter (Box 16, Folder 17)
  - EE 275, 1999-2000 Winter (Box 16, Folder 18)
  - EE 275, 1999-2000 Autumn (Box 16, Folder 19)
  - EE 275, 1998-1999 Summer (Box 16, Folder 20)
  - Curriculum Information, 1970, 1998-2000 (Box 16, Folder 21)
  - Past Exams - EE 275, 2001-2003 (Box 16, Folder 22)
  - EE 488 - Chapter 5, 1995 (Box 16, Folder 23)
  - Copy Order Form - SITN, 1989-1990 (Box 16, Folder 24)
  - ITC Tutorial Notes, 1997 (Box 16, Folder 25)
  - McCluskey tutorial notes, 1996 March (Box 16, Folder 26)
  - ITC Tutorial Notes, 1998 (Box 16, Folder 27)
  - EE 489, 1998 Spring (Box 16, Folder 28)
  - EE 275, 1998-1999 Winter (Box 16, Folder 29)
  - EE 275, 1998-1999 Autumn (Box 16, Folder 30)
  - EE 275, 1997-1998 Autumn (Box 16, Folder 31)
  - EE 381 Old Exams & Answers, 1999-2001 (Box 16, Folder 32)
  - EE 381, 1997 (Box 16, Folder 33)
  - EE 275, 1997-1998 Autumn (Box 16, Folder 34)
  - EE 381, 1996-1997 Autumn (Box 16, Folder 35)
  - EE 488, 2001-2002 Spring (Box 16, Folder 36)
  - EE 488, 1996 Spring (Box 16, Folder 37)
  - EE 488, 1999-2000 Spring (Box 16, Folder 38)
  - Class Grades, Emails, etc., 2001-2002 (Box 16, Folder 39)
  - RATS, 2001 April 30 (Box 16, Folder 40)
  - EE 275, 2004 Autumn (Box 16, Folder 41)
  - EE 275, 2003-2004 Winter (Box 16, Folder 42)
  - 311 Papers (Box 31)
  - EE275/ CS211 - Midterm Exam, 2001 (Box 31, Folder 13)
  - EE 489, Spring 1993-1994 (Box 34, Folder 1)
  - EE 489, Spring 1997-1998 (Box 34, Folder 2)
  - EE 383, Spring 1968 (Box 34, Folder 3)
  - EE 311, 1972 Spring (Box 34, Folder 4)
  - CS 311, Spring 1974 (Box 34, Folder 5)
  - CS311-EE482 (ISP/PMS), 1977, 1978 (Box 34, Folder 6)
- Chronological files
- Computer files
  - Floppy Disks with Lists of Files - Contains both PC & MAC Floppies (Box 33, Folder 13)
  - Floppy Disks with Lists of Files - Contains both PC & MAC Floppies (Box 33, Folder 14)
  - Floppy Disks with Lists of Files - Contains both PC & MAC Floppies (Box 33, Folder 15)
  - Floppy Disks, CM001-CM178 (Box 35)
  - Floppy Disks, CM179-CM337 (Box 36)
- Conference files
  - BIST Wokrshop - Charleston, SC, 1992 Mar 18-20 (Box 6, Folder 47)
  - Idea '92, 1992 Apr 14-16 (Box 6, Folder 48)
  - 1992 Conference Announcement (Box 6, Folder 49)
  - DFT Workshop - Vail, CO, 1992 Apr 21-24 (Box 6, Folder 50)
  - SDOC '92, 1992 Jun 11 (Box 6, Folder 51)
  - Computer Elements Vail Wokrshop - Vail, CO, 1992 Jun 21-24 (Box 6, Folder 52)
  - ONR Meeting - Arlington, WA, 1991 Jul 1-2 (Box 6, Folder 53)
  - 29th ACM/IEEE Design Automation Conference, 1992 May 27 (Box 6, Folder 54)
  - FTCS '92, 1992 Jul 8-10 (Box 6, Folder 55)
  - '92 Non-Conventional Faults in BiCOMS Digital Circuits MA & EJM, 1992 (Box 6, Folder 56)
  - ITC '92, 1992 Sep 20-24 (Box 6, Folder 57)
  - Hawaii Int'L Conference on System Sciences, Honolulu, hawaii, 1985 Jan. 2-4 (Box 20, Folder 24)
  - IEM Europe Institute Week 1: VLSI Design, Lech, Austria, 1985 June 23-29 (Box 20, Folder 25)
  - 22nd Design Automation Conference Las Vegas, Nevada, 1985 June 23-26 (Box 20, Folder 26)
  - Second European Workshop on Design for Testability, Stakis Dunblane Hydro, Scotland, 1984 May 21-24 (Box 20, Folder 27)
  - Third European Workshop on Design for Testability, Timmendorf, West Germany, 1985 June 11-13 (Box 20, Folder 28)
  - Electro/85 and Mini/Micro Northeast-85 Professional Program Participants New York, 1985 April 22-25 (Box 20, Folder 29)
  - The 15th IEEE Int'l Symp. on Fault Tolerant Computing (FTCS-15), Ann Arbor, Michigan, 1985 June 19-21 (Box 20, Folder 30)
  - 1995 International Test Conference - Washington D.C., 1995 October 23-25 (Box 21, Folder 30)
  - ITC, 1995 (Box 21, Folder 31)
  - ARPA - CSTO Joint PI Meeting - Fort Lauderdale, FL, 1995 July 10-14 (Box 21, Folder 32)
  - IFIP Meeting - Tahoe & FTCS - Pasadena, 1995 June 23-30 (Box 21, Folder 33)
  - ARGOS Meeting, 1995 June 21 (Box 21, Folder 34)
  - CRC Open House Conference, 1995 March 10 (Box 21, Folder 35)
  - 2nd International Test Synthesis Workshop - Santa Barbara, CA, 1995 May 7-10 (Box 21, Folder 36)
  - IEEE VTS - Princeton, NJ, 1995 April 30 - May 3 (Box 21, Folder 37)
  - Makar - Checking Experiments to Test Latches - 13th VLSI Test Symposium, 1995 April 30 - May 3 (Box 21, Folder 38)
  - Mukund - An Apparatus for Pseudo-Deterministic Testing - 13th VLSI Test Symposium, 1995 April 30- May 3 (Box 21, Folder 39)
  - Touba - Trabsfirned Psuedo-Random Patterns for BIST - 13th VLSI Test Symposium, 1995 April 30- May 3 (Box 21, Folder 40)
  - Touba - Transformed Pseudo-Random Patterns for BIST - BIST/DFT Workshop, 1995 (Box 21, Folder 41)
  - Touba 94 - Logic Synthesis Techniques for Reduced Area Implementation of... - Touba and EJM, 1994 (Box 21, Folder 42)
  - ITC - 94 - Washington, D.C., 1994 October 2-6 (Box 21, Folder 43)
  - ITC - 94 Special Papers, 1994 (Box 21, Folder 44)
  - Touba - Automated Logic Synthesis of Random Pattern Testable Circuits - Touba & EJM, 1994 (Box 21, Folder 45)
  - 1st International Test Synthesis Workshop - Santa Barbara, 1994 May 18-20 (Box 21, Folder 46)
  - Computer Elements Workshop - Vail, CO, 1994 June 26-29 (Box 21, Folder 47)
  - 1st Internation Test Synthesis Workshop - Santa Barbara, CA, 1994 May 18-20 (Box 21, Folder 48)
  - Open Faults in BiCMOS Gates - Ma & EJM, 1994 (Box 21, Folder 49)
  - On Line Delay Testing of Digital Circuits - 12th TEEE VLSI Test Symposium, 1993 April 25-28 (Box 21, Folder 50)
  - Honoris Causa - Grenoble France, 1994 April (Box 21, Folder 51)
  - Iternational Test Conference - Balitmore, MD, 1993 October 17-21 (Box 21, Folder 52)
  - AVRA - Synthesizing for Scan Dependence in Built-In Self-Testable Designs - Avra & EJM, 1993 (Box 21, Folder 53)
  - Hao - Very Low Voltage Testing for Weak CMOS Logic IC's - Hao & EJM, 1993 (Box 21, Folder 54)
  - McCluskey - Quality and Single Stuck Faults, 1993 (Box 21, Folder 55)
  - AT&T Conference on Electronic Testing - Princeton, NJ, 1993 September 27-28 (Box 21, Folder 56)
  - ILL - Talk at University of Illinois, 1993 September 23 (Box 21, Folder 57)
  - FTCS (Fault-Tolerant Computing - Toulouse, France, 1993 June 22-24 (Box 21, Folder 58)
  - Computer Elements Workshop - Vail, CO, 1993 June 20-23 (Box 21, Folder 59)
  - Computer Forum 25th Annual Meeting - Stanford University, CA, 1993 February 23-25 (Box 21, Folder 60)
  - ONR Meeting/ Tandem Visit - Austin, TX, 1993 January 11-14 (Box 21, Folder 61)
  - Computer Design Conference, 1984 Oct (Box 32, Folder 1)
  - Design for Testability - Vail, Colorado, 1983 Apr 12-14 (Box 32, Folder 2)
  - IEEE International Solid-State Circuits Conference - San Francisco, California, 1984 Feb 22-24 (Box 32, Folder 3)
  - Conference Papers (Box 32, Folder 4)
  - China Trip, 1980 Sep 19-30 (Box 32, Folder 5)
  - The 14th IEEE International Conference on Fault-Tolerant Computing - Orlando, Florida, 1984 Jun 20-22 (Box 32, Folder 6)
  - ARMS: Annual Reliablity & Maintainability Symposium - Philiadelphia, 1987 Jan 27-29 (Box 32, Folder 7)
  - Tektronimy Talk - Keroy, 1987 Apr 8 (Box 32, Folder 8)
  - The 10th Annual IEEE Design for Testability Workshop, 1987 Apr 21-23 (Box 32, Folder 9)
  - Denver-Lafayette Trip - Cancelled, 1988 Apr (Box 32, Folder 10)
  - Vail, Colorado, 1987 Apr 27 (Box 32, Folder 11)
  - IEEE Electron Device Society - San Diego, California, 1987 Apr 6 (Box 32, Folder 12)
  - Advanced Research in VLSI - "New Tech for New Arch", 1987 Mar 23-25 (Box 32, Folder 13)
  - ICCAD International Conference on Computing-Aided Design - Santa Clara, California, 1986 Nov 10-13 (Box 32, Folder 14)
  - FJCC Fall Joint Computer Conference - Dallas, Texas, 1986 Nov 2-4 (Box 32, Folder 15)
  - Test Tech Workshop - McClusky & Mourod, 1986 Sep 11 (Box 32, Folder 16)
  - International Test Conference on Testing's Impact on Design & Technology - Washington, D.C., 1986 Sep 8-11 (Box 32, Folder 17)
  - "Basic Concepts & Techniques of Hardware Fault Tolerance" - UC Santa Cruz, 1986 Aug 25 (Box 32, Folder 18)
  - D&T Editorial BD MTG - Las Vegas Hilton, Nevada, 1986 Jul 3 (Box 32, Folder 19)
  - UCSC "Hardware Fault Tolerance", 1986 Jul 14 (Box 32, Folder 20)
  - The 16th International Symposium on Fault-Tolerant Computing - Vienna, Austria, 1986 Jul 1-3 (Box 32, Folder 21)
  - "The Evolution of Fault-Tolerant Computing" Baden Symposium, 1986 Jun 30 (Box 32, Folder 22)
  - Fault-Tolerant Systems and Diagnostics Conference - Brno, Czechoslovakia, 1986 Jun 25-27 (Box 32, Folder 23)
  - ICCAD: Subcommittees Meeting - Estes Park, Colorado, 1986 Jun 8-10 (Box 32, Folder 24)
  - Dr. Pradhan: Comparing Causes IC Failure - University of Massachusetts/Amherst, 1986 May 14-17 (Box 32, Folder 25)
  - Custom Intergrated Circuits Conference at the Rochester Riverside Convention Center - Rochester, New York, 1986 May 12-15 (Box 32, Folder 26)
  - International Symposium on Circuits and Systems - San Jose, California, 1986 May 5-7 (Box 32, Folder 27)
  - Trip: DFT - Vail, Colorado & Albuquerque, 1986 April 28 - May 1 (Box 32, Folder 28)
  - Undetected Bad Chips, 1986 Apr 24 (Box 32, Folder 29)
  - Testing Workshop at University of Victoria - Victoria, British Columbia Canada, 1986 (Box 32, Folder 30)
  - IFIP Working Group 10.4 10th Meeting - Baden, 1986 Jun 27-30 (Box 32, Folder 31)
  - "Fundamental Mode and Pulse Mode Sequential Circuits", 1962 Aug 29-30 (Box 32, Folder 32)
  - IFIPS - Thos. Cook & Son, Correspondence, 1962 (Box 32, Folder 33)
  - IFIPS - Invitation, Planning, & Program, 1962 Aug (Box 32, Folder 34)
  - IFIP Congress: Symposium on Switching Theory - Munich, Germany, 1962 Aug 31 (Box 32, Folder 35)
  - Fudamental Mode & Pulse Mode Sequential Circuits - Princeton University, 1962 Aug (Box 32, Folder 36)
  - The 6th Annual Symposium on Circuit Theory & Logical Design - Ann Arbor, Michigan, 1965 Oct 6-8 (Box 32, Folder 37)
  - 7th Annual Symposium (Box 32, Folder 38)
  - Princeton Conference (Box 32, Folder 39)
  - Switching Theory & Logic Design TC - Part 1 (Box 32, Folder 40)
  - Switching Theory & Logic Design TC - Part 2 (Box 32, Folder 41)
  - Workshop on Distributed Fault-Tolerant Computers - San Juan, Puerto Rico, 1976 Nov 3-5 (Box 32, Folder 42)
  - Workshop on Reliability and Maintainbility of Computing Systems - Lake of the Ozarks, MO, 1969 Oct 20-22 (Box 32, Folder 43)